Guide to the S. D. House beekeeping materials, 1891-1947.
House, S.D. beekeeping materials, 1891-1947.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
S. D. House beekeeping materials, 1891-1947.
6384
S. D. House
2 cubic ft.
Photographs, letters, a typed manuscript, typed letters, diaries, and account books.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection relating to beekeeping business in Camillus, N.Y. includes: photographs, letters, a typed manuscript, typed letters, diaries, and account books. Also includes tintype of unidentified man and other miscellaneous materials.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection relating to beekeeping business in Camillus, N.Y. includes: photographs, letters, a typed manuscript, typed letters, diaries, and account books. Also includes tintype of unidentified man and other miscellaneous materials.
SUBJECTS
Names:
House, S. D.
Subjects:
Bee culture.; Beehives.; Beekeepers.; Honey.; Honeybees.
Places:
Camillus, (N.Y.)--Social life and customs.
Form and Genre Terms:
Account books.; Diaries.; Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Diaries
  - Child's diary, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Diary (not used), 1922 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Diary, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Journals/Diaries [some notes about beekeeping]
  - Journal/diary, 1891 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Journal/diary, 1893 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Journal/diary, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Journal/diary, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Journal/diary, 1899 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Journals/diaries, 1900-1901 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Journal/diary, 1902-1903 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Journal/diary, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Journal/diary, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Journal/diary, 1906 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Journal/diary, 1907-1908 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Journal/diary, 1908-1909 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Journal/diary, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Journal/diary, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Journal/diary, 1911 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Journal/diary, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Journal/diary, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Journal/diary, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Journal/diary, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Journal/diary, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Journal/diary, 1917 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Journal/diary, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Journal/diary, 1919 (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
  - Journal/diary, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Journal/diary, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Journal/diary, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Journal/diary, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Journal/diary, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Journal/diary, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Journal/diary, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Journal/diary, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Journal/diary, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Journal/diary, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Journal/diary, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Journal/diary, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Journal/diary, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Journal/diary, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Journal/diary, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Journal/diary, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Journal/diary, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Journal/diary, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Journal/diary, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Journal/diary, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Journal/diary, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Journal/diary, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Journal/diary, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Journal/diary, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Journal/diary, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Journal/diary, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Journal/diary, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Journal/diary, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Journal/diary, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Journal/diary, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Scrapbook
  - The Red Book (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Account books
  - Account book, 1893-1914 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Account book, 1899-1917 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Account book, 1913 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Account book, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
  - Account book, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Account book, 1928 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Account book, 1933 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Account book, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Account book, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Account book, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Account book, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Account book, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Account book, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Account book, 1941-1943 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Account book, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Account book, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 32-34)
- Miscellany
  - Address books, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 35-36)
  - New Testament, 1855 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Tintype, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Memo pad (blank), n.d. (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Check book, 1922 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Check book, 1923 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Memo book, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - New York State Grange directory, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Letters to Mr. S.D. House; various business receipts, articles, photographs, bee inspector license, 1894-1934 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Photo of Glen Side Apiaries Exhibit, S.D. House, Camillus, N.Y. (over/size mounted prints [2]), n.d. (Box 1, Folder 44-45)